adwatcher.net 2006-06-15

# AdWatcher - Advertising Manager, Return on Investment (ROI) Tracker, Fraud Monitor

**What is the purpose of this Privacy Policy?**

MordComm, Inc. has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our users. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.AdWatcher.com. Please continue reading for complete details on the MordComm, Inc. privacy policy. 

**What information do we collect from users and how is it used?**

MordComm, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy. 

**Surveys & Contests **

From time-to-time, our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Referral Program**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend or colleague about our site, we ask for the friend's name and E-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time E-mail inviting them to visit the site. MordComm, Inc. applies the same privacy protection for all referrals and third party information that is provided by a user. Their information is stored for the sole purpose of sending this one-time E-mail. The friend may contact us to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Correspondence**

If you correspond with us via E-mail or snail mail, or if other third parties such as hosting suppliers provide us with information about you, we may gather the information in a file specific to you. We only collect the Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to us. While we may gather market data from other resources, the scope of our knowledge about Personally Identifiable Information based upon your use of our site is entirely up to you. Like many other websites, MordComm, Inc. collects information about users' utilization and navigation of our site. This information helps us to design our site to better suit our users' needs. For example, our site will track the URL that you visited before you came to our site, the URL to which you next go and your Internet Provider (IP) address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site. Your IP address also is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

**How does a customer 'opt-in' or 'opt-out' of MordComm, Inc. promotional E-mail?**

Our users are given the opportunity to opt-in to receive promotional E-mail at the time of registration. Promotional E-mail does not include E-mail necessary for our site's services. We ask that a customer actively check a box to receive E-mail about special offers and hosting tips. At anytime a user can request removal from the distribution list. 

**Does the MordComm, Inc. website use cookies? If so, how are cookies used on the website?**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to a user's hard drive for record-keeping purposes while visiting a site. Like most major websites, MordComm, Inc. uses cookies on certain pages of our site. Cookies make using the Internet easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. For example, a cookie lets the MordComm, Inc. website remember that you've registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at our site, and which allows you to enter your password less frequently while visiting our website. We may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Our cookies do not contain any content specific information. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information although cookies may enable us to relate your use of our website to personally identifying information that you previously submitted. For example, it enables us to enhance personalization on the website, such as calling you by name when you return to our site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, although your browser may permit you to decline cookies. If you do decline cookies, your use of our site may be slowed because you may need to re-enter information. 

**What are the policies of linked sites and other third parties?**

This privacy policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Although you may interact with hosting suppliers as a result of visiting our site, or link to other sites or third parties via our website, MordComm, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or the content of linked sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy policy whenever interacting with any website. 

**To whom does MordComm, Inc. release information?**

Please be aware that despite our best intentions and the guidelines outlined in this privacy policy, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Moreover, we may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or to third parties under certain circumstances, such as illegal activity on our Site. MordComm, Inc. reserves the right to release personally identifiable information to law enforcement or other government officials, as MordComm, Inc., in our sole and absolute discretion, deems necessary or appropriate. 

**How will I know about changes in the Privacy Policy?**

MordComm, Inc. reserves the right to update this privacy policy from time to time. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes. However, we will only use Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the Privacy Policy that was in effect at the time the information was collected. If at any point we should decide to use that information differently, we will notify users by way of E-mail so that users can approve or disapprove of such use.
